Hey, Chandler, why do you think they call it foosball?
嘿, 錢德, 你覺得他們為什麼叫它足"求"?
- Know what I like about you, Joe? - What?
- 知道我喜歡你哪點嗎, 喬伊? - 哪點?
You're curious.
你愛提問.
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嘿. - 嗨.
I'll drop Emma off at my mom's if we're still on tonight.
如果我們今晚繼續 我就把艾瑪放在我媽那
- Oh, you bet. Yeah. - Okay.
- 噢, 肯定. 是的. - 好的.
- Say, "Bye." - Bye.
- 說 "拜拜" - 拜拜.
- Bye. - Bye.
- 拜. - 拜.
- So you and Rachel tonight, huh? - Yeah.
-今晚和瑞秋有約，呃？ -對
Yeah, it's actually our first official date.
我們第一次正式約會。
Wow, so tonight may be the night. You nervous?
哇！看樣子今晚有事發生！ 你緊張嗎？
No. This is the part I'm actually good at.
不，不。這是我最擅長的。
What must it be like not to be crippled by fear and self-loathing?
即使是恐懼和自我厭惡情緒也不能產生影響？
It's okay.
對！
How can you be so confident?
你怎麼能這麼有信心？
Well, I know exactly what I'm gonna do.
呃，我……因為我明確地知道我要做什麼！
- Really? Like, you have a routine? - No. See, each woman is different.
- 真的？就像例行公事？ - 不不不。知道嗎，女人個個都不同。
You have to appreciate their uniqueness.
你要欣賞到她們的特性。
- Really? - No, I do six things.
- 真的？ - 不，我會做六件事！
First, I look deep into her eyes, then I kiss her.
首先，我要深情地望著她的眼睛 然後，我會吻她。
Next, I take my hand and I softly graze her thigh.
隨後我用手輕輕地擦過她的大腿
You mean like this?
你是說這樣？
No, not like that. No, no. No, like this:
不！不是像那樣，不不。 是像這樣
I see what you mean. That's quite nice.
噢，我知道你的意思了，真的感覺很棒。
- More foosball? - And beer.
- 再來一局桌上足球？ - ……還有啤酒！！
The One With Ross's Tan
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
Hey, sweetie.
嗨，親愛的！
Hey, stop staring at my wife's legs.
嘿！不許看我老婆的腿！
No, no. Stop staring at your sister's legs.
不不！不許看你妹妹的腿！
I'm sorry, it's just.. How'd you get so tan?
對不起，只是…… 你怎麼曬得皮膚？
She went to one of those spray-on tan places.
她去了一個那種噴霧曬膚俱樂部
That was supposed to be a secret.
那應該是個秘密.
Did I say spray-on tan places?
我是說的噴霧曬膚俱樂部?
I meant surf contest.
我是說衝浪競賽.
Which she won.
她獲勝的那個.
You got a spray-on tan?
呃，你做了噴霧曬膚？
Chandler gets pedicures!
錢德去美甲了！
What? You do? Like, with the toe separators?
什麼？你做了美甲？ 你用了那種腳趾隔離器？
Why? Why?
為……為什麼？
I can't believe that's sprayed on.
我還是不能相信那是噴霧曬膚的結果……
I mean, it looks really good. I wonder if I should get one.
我是說，這看起來不錯 我也想做一次！
Sure, then you should get a miniskirt so you can really show it off.
當然，然後你應該穿上超短裙去街上秀給別人看。
So do you get colors or just French tips?
那麼，你是塗了趾甲油還是只留了法式的長趾甲？
- Here. Here's their card. - Thanks.
- 在這兒。我這兒有張卡。 - 謝謝。
Hey, I know where this place is.
嗨，我知道這個地方！
It used to be an X-rated video..
那兒曾經是個成人錄影帶……
Florist.
花店。
- Hey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-嗨！ -嗨！菲比！
You won't believe who moved back to town.
噢，你們不會相信誰搬回來了。
I know. Amanda.
我知道，阿蔓達！
- She called me too. She's the worst. - Who's Amanda?
-啊！她也給我打電話了！她是最差勁的！ -誰是阿蔓達？
She's this girl who lived in the building before you did.
她是你搬進來以前住你那間房子的女人。
Then she moved to England and picked up this fake British accent.
後來她搬去英國了， 還學了假惺惺的英國口音。
On the machine, this is her message:
她在我留言機上的留言是這樣的：
"Monica, darling, it's Amanda calling."
「莫妮卡，親愛的！ 阿蔓達在給你打電話！」
Are you trying to do a British accent?
你是要模仿英國口音？
Chandler gets pedicures.
錢德去美甲了！
Just so I know, how many more of those can I expect?
我只想知道 我還要受多少次這種奚落？
Know what Amanda said when she called me?
你知道阿蔓達跟我是在電話上是怎麼說的？
"Oh, so sorry to catch you on your mobile."
「哦，很抱歉打你的手機！
If you didn't wanna get me on my mobile, then don't call me on my mobile.
如果—如果你不想跟我在手機上說 那就別給我手機打電話！」
And she always brags about all the famous people she's met.
我知道， 她還老是拿她碰到的名人來吹牛。
Oh, I know!
噢，我知道！
"I slept with Billy Joel."
「哦……我跟喬爾.比利睡覺了」。
All right, who hasn't?
好吧，可那是誰？
What are we gonna do? I don't wanna see her.
噢，我們該怎麼辦？ 我不想見她！
Let's just cut her out.
呃，我們隔離了她！
- What? - Cut her out of our lives.
- 什麼？ -把她從我們的生活裡隔離！
Just ignore her calls and dodge her till she gets the point.
不理她的電話， 躲開她直到她明白過來！
Well, I guess we could try that. But it seems so harsh.
哦，我覺得我們可以試試， 不過……有點太苛刻了吧！
- Have you ever done that? - No. Had it done to me, though.
- 你這麼做過嗎？ - 沒，不過有人對我做過。
Feels good.
感覺不錯！
All right, Mr. Geller, right this way.
好的蓋勒先生！ 請走這邊！
So how dark do you wanna be? We have one, two or three.
那麼，你想要多深呢？ 我們有一級、二級和三級。
Well, I like how you look. What are you?
呃……我喜歡你的顏色 你是什麼等級的？
- Puerto Rican. - Two. I think a two.
- 我是波多黎各人。 - 二級，我想要二級。
You'll face the red light.
你要面對著紅燈。
When the light's on, the spraying's about to start, so close your eyes.
紅燈亮的時候噴淋開始， 所以，閉上眼睛
When the spraying stops, count to five..
噴淋停止的時候，數五下。
pat yourself to avoid drip marks, then turn to get your back. Got it?
向後仰一點防止出現液體流下的痕跡 然後轉身我們就可以噴你背後了。明白了？
Spray, count, pat and turn. Spray, count and pat.
噴，數，仰，然後轉，噴，數，仰。
- You catch on quick. - Well, I have a Ph.D., so..
- 哇，你掌握得真快。 - 那當然，我有個PHD，所以……
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three..
一隻綿羊，兩隻綿羊，三隻綿……
Wait, wait! I'm not.. I'm not finished counting!
等等！等等！我還沒…… 我還沒數完呢！！
You sprayed my front twice!
你噴了我正面兩次！
- You never turned? - No! I barely got to "three Mississippi"!
- 你沒轉身嗎？ -沒有，我甚至還沒數到三隻綿羊呢。
Mississippi? I said count to five.
綿羊？ 我是說數到五！
Mississippi-less-ly?
不要綿羊？
Well, how bad is it?
好吧，那這有多糟糕？
Not that bad yet. But it gets darker for the next four hours.
不會多糟糕的 不過隨後的四個小時顏色會變得越來越深。
- So how dark will it get? - You got sprayed with two twos and..
- 那麼，會變得多深？ - 你噴了兩遍二級而且……
I'm a four?
我是四級的了？
Yeah, but your back's a zero. You'll wanna even that out.
對，不過你背上是零級。 你想讓前後一樣
Really?
是吧?
- You might wanna get back in there. - Oh, okay!
- 你可能要再進去一次。 - 好吧！
Wait a minute, there's no light on the back wall.
等等，等等， 後面牆上沒有燈！
How do I know when it's gonna start? Hello?
我怎麼知道它什麼時候開始？ 有人嗎？
My eyes!
我的眼睛！
The same thing happened again!
我重蹈了自己的覆轍！
- You got two more twos? - I'm an eight!
- 你又做了兩次二級？ - 我是八級的了！
Thanks for dinner.
謝謝你的晚餐。
I thought you paid.
我還以為是你付的錢呢。
Guess we won't be going back there.
哈，看來我們以後再也不會去那兒了。
- So.. - Yeah.
- 那麼。 - 好吧。
Hey, what do you say we move this onto the likes of the couch?
嘿，我們到沙發上去 你說怎麼樣？
I say cheesy line, but okay.
我要說『爛主意』，不過，行。
- What's the matter? - I don't know. I'm sorry.
- 怎麼了？ - 對不起，我也不知道，對不起，
- I don't know why I did that. - Okay.
- 我不知道為什麼那麼做！ - 好吧。
Okay. Sorry.
真對不起。
I'm sorry. Again, I don't know what happened. I must be nervous.
再一次，對不起！我不知道…我怎麼了 我一定是太緊張了！
I don't get it. Chandler loved it.
我搞不懂，錢德很喜歡的！
I promise. I won't do it again. I really do. This is gonna be great.
好吧，我保證，我保證，我不會再這麼做了。 真的，我保證。這次會很完美的。
- Okay. - Okay.
- 好吧。 - 好吧。
Was that good for you?
呃，你喜歡這樣?
No, don't get it. Let the machine pick up.
不，不，別接。 讓答錄機接。
Yeah, it could be Rachel asking if someone could babysit again.
哦，對 可能又是瑞秋要我們幫她看孩子。
- It could be Amanda. - Oh, you're right.
- 可能是阿蔓達！ - 哦，對了！
I was just kidding about Rachel. Babysitting's a gas.
我只是拿瑞秋開玩笑的。 看孩子很好玩！
Hello, Monica. It's Amanda calling again.
莫妮卡，你好。 是阿蔓達又打來電話。
I'm in the neighborhood, hoping I could pop by your flat.
我就在隔壁 想到你家來坐坐。
You're from Yonkers! Your last name is Buffamonteezi!
你來自揚克斯！ 你姓Buffo-Martisis！
Let's see. So should you get this directly..
我看……為了確保你知道了
ring me back on my mobile.
給我的手機回電話
Okay, don't hold thy breath.
好了，別憋住氣說話！
- Hello? Is someone on the line? -  Yes. I was looking for Monica.
- 喂？有人在用電話嗎？ -  對，我在找莫妮卡。
Hang on, she's right here.
等等，她在這兒。
- Someone's on the phone for you. - We weren't picking up. It's Amanda.
- 有人打電話，找你的。 - 我們在過濾電話呢，是阿蔓達！
I get pedicures.
我做美甲了！
Hi, Amanda.
嗨，阿蔓達！
Actually, now is not a good time.
實際上……現在……現在不太合適。
Dinner tomorrow night?
明晚一起吃晚飯？
Okay, Phoebe and I will see you then.
好的，我和菲比都會到的！
Why? Why? Why didn't you just say no?
為什麼，為什麼，為什麼你不拒絕！
Well, I said no to her coming over now. I couldn't say no twice.
呃，我已經拒絕讓她來了！ 我不能拒絕她兩次！
I got this uncontrollable need to please people.
我有種不由自主地取悅別人的需要！
Fine. Fine. You would not hold up well under torture.
好吧，好吧！ 一拷問你就會招的！
- Oh, and you would? - I did.
- 那你呢？ - 我已經招了！
- Rach, are you sure you wanna do this? - Absolutely.
- 瑞秋，你確定你想嗎？ - 當然！當然！
It's just a little weird. It's you, and it's me.
我……只是有點奇怪，是你和我
- It'll just take some getting used to. - Okay.
- 我們需要點時間來習慣。 - 好吧。
Okay, well, how can we make it easier?
啊… 我們怎麼能讓這個變得容易點？
Okay. Let's work from the top down.
好吧，讓我們從上往下！
- Just work the bra, Joe. - Okay, got it, yeah. Absolutely.
- 解開我的胸罩，喬伊！ - 好的，呃，明白了。
- Okay. - Okay.
- 好吧。 - 好吧。
- Is this thing welded shut? - Okay.
- 這玩意兒焊住了嗎？！ - 哦！.
- You want a little help? - No.
- 要我幫忙嗎？ - 不！
- Okay. - I can handle it. Okay?
- 好吧！ - 我能處理這個！
- I've been opening these since I was 9. - Nine?
-我9歲的時候就會了。 - 9歲就會了？
- What kind of 9-year-old girl wears a bra? - No, no. I was 9.
- 9歲的女孩穿胸罩？ - 不，不，是我9歲的時候。
See, she was 16. Okay? Yeah.
呃，她16歲?
My parents had.. I can't talk and work at the same time!
我爸爸媽媽已經… 哦！我不能一邊說一邊做！
All right, turn around. I gotta get a look at this thing.
好了，轉個身，我得看看這東西。
Sorry.
對不起！
Well, this is romantic.
這真夠浪漫的！
I'm sorry. This has never happened to me before.
對不起！ 這種事從來沒有發生在我身上！
I'm an expert at taking off bras. I could do it with one hand.
我是解胸罩的專家！ 我一隻手就能解開！
I could do it with my eyes closed. Once I just looked at one..
我閉著眼睛也行！ 有一次我只看了一眼
and it popped open.
它自己就開了！
- I blame your bra. - It's a standard-issue bra clasp.
- 都怪你的胸罩！ - 這是個標準型的胸罩搭扣！
Then I blame you. Yeah. That's right. You threw me off with all your slapping.
那就怪你！對！ 是你把我的天賦都打走了！
Okay, look, I'm really sorry about that, Joey.
好吧，我真的 真的很抱歉，喬伊！
But do you think maybe, on some level, you don't want to take off my bra?
可你想過嗎？ 可能是你潛意識裡不想脫掉我的胸罩？
No, I don't have another level.
啊！我沒有那種潛意識！！
Hi.
嗨！
Oh, dear God.
哦，天啊！
Hold on. There's something different.
等等！有點不對勁。
I went to that tanning place your wife suggested.
我去了你老婆推薦的地方。
Was that place the sun?
那那個地方……是太陽？
Oh, and it gets worse.
哦！比那還糟！
Oh, my God, you can do a duet of "Ebony and lvory" all by yourself.
哦，天吶！ 你一個人就能同時表現黑檀木和象牙!
How could you mess this up? It's so easy.
你怎麼能搞成這樣？ 這很容易呀！
You go in the booth, count to five and turn around.
你進到小隔間裡 數到五，轉身！！
- How do you count to five? - One, two, three..
- 你是怎麼數到五的？ - 一、二、三……
Damn it!
可惡！
I know!
我知道！
What is up with Miss Hawaiian Tropic?
噢，哦！偏移的熱帶發生了什麼？
How was your date with Joey?
你和喬伊的約會怎麼樣？
Well, it was good, until we got back to our apartment.
嗯，還不錯…… 至少在我們回家之前
And then we were fooling around and he started to put his hand up my leg..
後來我們就搞砸了 他把手放在我的腿上
and I kept slapping it away.
可我卻不停的打開它！
You didn't like that?
你不喜歡？
Well, it wasn't just me, all right? He freaked out too.
嗯，不光是我，明白嗎？ 他也出問題了！
He couldn't even undo my bra.
他甚至解不開我的胸罩！
Really? One time he just looked at my bra and it popped open.
哇，真的？有一次 他只看了我的胸罩一眼，它就自己崩開了。
I do not know what's wrong with us.
我不知道我們怎麼了
We've kissed before and that's been great.
我是說 我們以前接吻過，那很好！
But this time it was leading somewhere..
可是，可是這次
and I was very aware of the fact that it was Joey touching me.
我明白那是喬伊在撫摸我。
You guys have been friends forever.
呃，你們要永遠做朋友了。
The first time you kissed Ross was weird.
記得你第一次吻羅斯嗎? 那次多奇怪！
You couldn't stop laughing. You got through that.
你不停的笑？ 可你渡過了。
Okay. That's true. That's true, we can do this.
對，是這樣。 是這樣，我們能行。
You're right. We can do this. We'll just power through.
對，對，我們能行。 我們有能力渡過！
Chandler, can I talk to you for a second?
嗨，錢德 我能跟你談談嗎？
No need, problem solved. We are powering through.
沒必要了！！ 問題解決了，我們要努力渡過。
Chandler, stop. It's not going to pop open.
錢德，停下！他不會崩開的。
You don't know.
你怎麼知道！
- Hi, Phoebe. - Hey.
- 嗨，菲比！ - 嗨！
- Is Amanda here yet? - No.
- 阿蔓達來了嗎？ - 還沒。
I'm sorry for screwing up that "cutting her out" plan, but I have a new plan.
好吧，我很抱歉搞砸了那個隔離她的計劃。 不過我有了個新計劃。
Chandler will call in a few minutes with an emergency.
錢德答應我幾分鐘以後給我打個緊急電話。
Okay, what kind of emergency gets us both out of here?
哦！ 那，什麼緊急的事情能把我們兩個人都叫走呢？
What do you think of Mike and Chandler being in a car accident?
這樣，你覺得麥克和錢德出了車禍怎麼樣？
- Are you kidding? I love it! - Okay.
- 你開玩笑，我太喜歡了！ - 好！
- Hi. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
Hello!
你好！
It's so nice to see you.
看到你們真好！
Both of you, look at me. Look how young I look!
你們兩個！看看我。 看我看起來多年輕！
Oh, gosh, we have so much to catch up on.
噢，天吶！ 我們有太多的事情要分享了！
But first things first. Touch my abs. I don't exercise at all.
不過最首要的是： 摸摸我的腹肌，我一點兒都沒鍛煉！
Oh, gosh. So, Monica, you're married.
噢，天吶，莫妮卡，你結婚了！
- Yeah, his name is Chandler and he's.. - Oh, smell my neck.
- 對！對！他叫錢德而且…… - 聞聞我的脖子！
It's not perfume. It's me. It's my natural scent.
這不是香水！這是我！ 這是我自然的體香！
Musty.
發霉了！
Gosh, this is brilliant. Gosh, it's just like old times.
噢！天吶！這太完美了。 天吶，就像以前一樣，
I'm so happy you two are friends again.
真高興看到你們倆又和好了！
- When were we not friends? - Well, it was 1992.
- 我們什麼時候不是朋友了？ - 呃，是1992年，
And I remember, because that was the year I had sex with Evel Knievel.
我記得是因為那年我和肯尼.伊夫上床了。
We were friends in 1992.
呃，1992年我們是朋友啊。
No, I distinctly remember you were dodging her calls..
不，我清楚地記得你當時在過濾她的電話，
and trying to avoid seeing her.
還盡量不見她。
- You were going to cut me out? - Well, kind of.
- 你在隔離我？ - 呃……差不多吧。
- Oh, my God! - Oh, bugger.
- 噢，我的天！ - 噢！見鬼。
Should I not have said that? I feel like a perfect arse.
我是不是不該說？ 我覺得自己就像個飯桶！
Well, in America, you're just an ass.
對，對，不過在美國你只是個蠢蛋！
Hello?
喂？
Chandler, what's wrong?
錢德，怎麼了？
Oh, my God, are you all right? Yeah, I'll be right there.
噢，天吶，你沒事吧？ 好的，我馬上到。
I'm so sorry, but Chandler was in a car accident.
對不起。錢德出車禍了。
- Oh, my God. - Yeah.
- 噢，我的天。 - 噢！
- Was Mike with him? - Nope.
- 麥克跟他一起嗎？ - 沒！
- Got the champagne? - Yes. Ready to power through.
- 買了香檳了？ - 是，女士，準備好加速過渡了！
Excellent. Put it on ice, the phone is off the hook..
太棒了！把它放到冰桶裡 電話線已經拔了
and, in the interest of powering through..
集中精力加速過渡！
Oh, sure. Now. Yeah.
哦，好，現在
Okay, sexy..
好了，性感點兒，性感點兒 性感點兒
very sexy. Sexy. All right, let's do it!
很性感 好了！我們開始！
Okay, you're scaring me a little bit.
好的，你有點兒嚇到我了。
Get over it, soldier, we gotta do this.
噢！過來大兵，我們要開始了！
- Okay. You like that, huh? - Oh, yeah.
- 好的，啊！你喜歡是不是？ - 哦，是的。
You like that? Let's kick this into high gear, huh?
你喜歡嗎？我們開始換到高速檔。
Yeah, baby! I'll show you how we do it!
對，寶貝兒， 我來告訴你我們怎麼做！
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
You kneed me in my misters!
你頂住我的小先生了！
What? Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
什麼？噢，天吶！ 對不起
Joey? Are you okay?
喬伊？你還好嗎？
Soldier down.
大兵犧牲了！
We are not friends with Phoebe anymore.
我們和菲比不再是朋友了。
If she asks, I protested a little, but okay.
要是她問起來 我會表示一點抗議，不過沒問題！
I just found out that she tried cutting me out.
我剛知道，她曾經試圖隔離我！
Can you think of any reason why someone would want to do that?
你有沒有想過人為什麼那樣做？
What is wrong with me, Chandler? Tell me.
我怎麼了，錢德？告訴我
I had a very bad car accident.
我出了嚴重的車禍！
Chandler, thank God you're alive. Monica, can I talk to you outside?
噢，錢德！感謝上帝你還活著。 莫妮卡，能和你到外面談談嗎？
- I have nothing to say to you. - My flat is twice this size.
- 我跟你沒什麼可說的。 - 哇，我的房子有這兩個大！
You know, they asked me to be one of the Spice Girls.
你要知道, 他們曾經邀我參加辣妹組合
Please, Monica, in the hall?
好嘛，莫妮卡！去走廊裡？
Oh, that accident must have been terrible.
噢，那場車禍一定很恐怖。
You look positively ghastly.
你看起來臉色蒼白得厲害。
Well, aren't you a treat.
好了，你不開心嗎？
I can't believe you tried to cut me out. Why, Phoebe? Why?
我簡直不能相信你要隔離我。 為什麼菲比，為什麼？
It was right after we were living together..
那是在我們住在一起以後
and you were driving me crazy, okay?
你快要把我逼瘋了，知道嗎？
You were really controlling and compulsive and shrill.
你什麼都要控制，強制，還要尖叫。
Well, I'm still all those things!
我現在仍然這樣！
You're also so generous and kind and scrappy.
你現在還很慷慨 善良，鬥志旺盛！
I am scrappy.
我鬥志旺盛。
Exactly. No matter what I tried to do, I couldn't keep you out of my life.
當然！看，無論我要做什麼 我都不能把你從生活中剔除。
Of all the people I've cut out..
在我隔離的所有人中
you were the only one who ever clawed her way back in.
你是唯一一個我又把她拉回來的。
That's because I'm scrappy.
因為我鬥志旺盛？
Yeah, you are, and I'm so glad that you fought your way back in..
對，是的。 而且我也很高興你通過鬥爭又回來了，
because I don't know what I would do without you.
因為我不知道沒有你該怎麼辦。
I don't know what I would do without you.
我也不知道沒有你該怎麼辦。
Well, I guess we should go back in. I mean, you gave me another chance.
好吧，我想我們該回去了 既然你又給了我一次機會
- We should do the same for Amanda. - Yeah, I guess you're right.
- 我們應該用同樣的方法對付阿蔓達  - 對，你說得對。
Can you believe it? I've never had any professional dance training.
你能相信嗎？ 我從來沒有受過專業舞蹈訓練。
Now, let me explain how this works. You go into the booth and..
現在我來給你解釋她是怎麼工作的。 你走進隔間，然後……
I'm gonna stop you right there, Glenda. Okay?
就說到這兒吧，葛蘭達。好嗎？
Does it look like this is my first time?
我看起來像是第一次嗎？呃？
Now, I want four two's, and I want them all on my back.
我現在想要一個四倍的二級 ……而且我想都噴到背上。
Okay.
好吧……
Wait. There's two sets of nozzles! Which one is it? Which one is it?
等等，這兒有兩套噴嘴兒 應該用哪一個？哪個……哪個才是？
Oh, son of a bitch!
哦！渾蛋！
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑嗎？
- How did we do? - I'm a twelve.
- 我們干怎麼辦？ - 我只有12歲！
What is the matter with us?
我們到底怎麼了？
Well, I know what's the matter with me.
呃，我知道我到底怎麼了。
No, I mean with us, you know? I mean, is it supposed to be this..
不，我是說我們，知道嗎。 我是說，真的應該這麼……
difficult?
困難嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
That fake British woman's a real bitch, but she sure can dance.
這個假惺惺英國腔的女人真是個婊子 可她還真的以為自己會跳舞……
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
Hey, listen, can I ask you a question? When you and Monica first hooked up..
嘿，聽著，能問你個問題嗎？ 你和莫妮卡剛好上的時候
was it weird going from friends to more than that?
從朋友到超越那層關係的時候有什麼怪事嗎？
Kind of. Sneaking around, having to hide from you guys..
應該……你知道， 到處躲藏，跟你們玩捉迷藏……
No, no, no. No, I mean..
不，不，不……不是 我是說……
sexually.
性方面……
Yeah, was there a part of you that felt like it was..
呃，是不是你們倆某方面 ……感覺……
really wrong?
這麼做不對？
Actually, no. No, it felt right, you know?
實際上，不是。 沒有，感覺很好。
If felt like, "I can't believe we haven't been doing this the whole time."
知道嗎，感覺就像 呃……我不能相信我們居然一直沒這麼做。
I can tell from your expressions that's the good news you were hoping for.
我能從你們的話裡聽出來， 好消息是你們想……
Well, I'm gonna go continue to spread the joy.
好吧，我想我該做的是 ……繼續傳播快樂。
Just because it happened that way for them doesn't mean it has to for us.
好吧 他們的反應是那樣的不見得我們也要那樣。
Yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
對，對……完全正確。
I mean, just because something's difficult doesn't mean that you quit.
我是說，事情困難並不意味著你要退卻。
- Right, totally. - Yeah. And so..
- 完全正確。 - 好吧
we'll just keep trying and trying until we do it.
那我們會不停地試啊 試啊，直到我們……成功。
If not, we'll just be a couple that never has sex.
對，如果不行的話， 我們就作為一一對沒有性愛的夫婦吧。
That's a plan.
這也是個……計劃。
- I did not see this coming. - I know.
- 哇……我看這種事不會發生。 - 我知道。
I don't know, I don't get it. I mean, I was so sure this is what I wanted.
那我就不明白了。 我說，我很確定我確實需要啊。
Me too.
呃……我也是……
Well, how come Monica and Chandler could do it?
我想知道莫妮卡和錢德是怎麼做到的？
I guess they weren't as good friends as we are.
我想或許他們不像我們是一對這麼好的朋友吧。
I bet you're right.
我想你肯定是對的。
So..
那麼……
Yeah.
好吧。
I love you.
我愛你。
Love you too.
我也愛你。
- All right, I'm going to bed. - Yeah, me too.
- 好了，我要去睡覺了。 - 好，我也是。
Yeah. I'm not going anywhere for a while.
噢，對了 暫時我還不想去任何地方。
- Dude, it's Chandler. Let me in. - Go away!
- 哥們兒，是錢德。讓我進來。 -走開！
I don't wanna see anybody!
我誰都不想見。
I went to the tanning place and the same thing happened to me. Let me in.
我知道，我也去了那個地方 而且同樣的事也發生在我身上了。 讓我進來。
Really?
真的？
Did you count Mississippi-ly?
你也數了小綿羊？
You're not tan.
夥計，你沒去曬。
No. I just had to get a picture of this. I'll see you later.
沒，我只是來拍張照 我會來看你的！